So for starters I'm going to show you all what we need.
I've got a plate of boneless, skinless chicken breast here, the frozen kind so I let them defrost.
I've got a large onion, a medium size green bell pepper, I've got pepper, some butter and I've got a brush so you can brush our casserole dish right here, our casserole dish with a little butter.
We've got a package which is regular Ranch salad dressing.
We've got some garlic powder, some Adobe seasoning, a little hot sauce some salt.
Let's see we've got flour tortillas, the jumbo kind, mozzarella cheese and a fiesta blend cheese or you could use Colby-Jack.
I've got some oil here, so we cook our chicken in our skillet.
I've got some just regular tomato salsa.
Now the thing is you really want to use a whole jar of this but if your short like I am you can just use a can of tomatoes and just grind it up in your food processor.
Here I've got onion and garlic tomatoes that's just going to make everything taste better.
I guess will get started.
Oh and by the way we have a mixing bowl here because you may need one of those.